Inventory of the Papers of Monroe Leigh, 1941 - 2001
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- International Criminal Court (ICC)
  - ABA War Crimes Task Force - Yugoslavia
    - Monroe Leigh Notebooks Vol. 1, including Index [1993] (Box-folder 26 - 7)
      Contains index to Vol. 1 - Vol. 4, Annotated Agenda, Notice of meeting with questions, Meron article, US Proposal, Secretary General's Report, Membership List, Outline of ABA Report, Minutes of May 19, 1993 Meeting, Notices of Second Meeting of Task Force (Mary 24, 1993, May 27, 1993, June 1, 1993), Preliminary Draft Report, Minutes of June 2d Meeting, June 8 letter to Rashkow Re Chief Prosecutor Recommendations, Monroe Leigh signature, check marks, handwritten notations, post-it notes
    - Monroe Leigh Notebooks Vol. 2 [1993] (Box-folder 26 - 8)
      Contains June 10 Memo on Meeting June 14 (bound separately) - Proposed agenda, Second draft including executive summary and red lined copy of report, Memo on role of federal judge in grand jury proceedings and military justice practice, Monroe Leigh signature, handwritten notations, edits
    - Monroe Leigh Notebooks Vol. 3 [1993] (Box-folder 26 - 9)
      Contains June 17 memo on Meeting June 25 (Proposed Agenda, Revised Executive Summary of Report, Revised draft resolution), Minutes of June 14 meeting, June 22 memo transmitting final draft, Minutes of June 25 meeting, June 25 memo advising of further meeting on Monday, June 28 to finish report, Minutes of June 28 meeting, June 29 memo advising of meeting Thursday, July 1 to finalize report, Monroe Leigh signature, underlinds, handwritten edits, notations,
    - Monroe Leigh Notebooks Vol. 4 [1993] (Box-folder 27 - 1)
      Contains June 30 memo transmitting final draft and advising of meeting July 1 with agenda, June 30 memo transmitting Dod Draft of Procedural Rules for the Tribunal, June 30 memo listing recommendations for Judges of Tribunal, Minutes of July 1 meeting, June 12 memo enclosing final version of the Task Force Report and mintues for meetings of June 25, June 28 and July 1. (Final version is velo bound separate document), Monroe Leigh signature
    - Task Force Resumes, 1991 - 1993 (Box-folder 27 - 2)
      Contains resumes of potential members of the task force, a copy of the New York Times Magazine April 21, 1991 Section 6 "Capture of a Terrorist" by Steven Emerson sent by Victoria Toensing to Monroe Leigh, highlights, edits, checkmarks, memos
  - United Nations (UN)
    - ILC: "Report of the International Law Commission on the work of its Forty-Sixth Session", 1 May - 22 July 1994 (Box-folder 27 - 3)
      Includes post-it indicated item is on disk
    - ILC: "Report of the International Law Commission on the Work of its Forty-Sixth Session", 1 September 1994 (Box-folder 27 - 4)
      Handwritten comments and highlighting
    - Report of the Preparatory Committee on the Establishment of an International Criminal Court including A/Conf.183/2/Add.1 (Part 2 of report) (Box-folder 27 -)
      no markup and can find online at: http://www.un.org/law/n9810105.pdf
    - Commission of Experts established pursuant to Security Council Resolution 780 (1992), s/1994/674, 27 May 1994 &,amp, Annexes: Volume 1 - Final Report &,amp, Annexes I through V, 10 February 1995 (Box-folder 27 - 5)
      Contains underlining, check marks, and Monroe Leigh's signature, notecard from M. Cherif Bassiouni
    - Fax to Sharon McHale from Monroe Leigh, contains Leigh Bio and Resume, 8 February 1999 (Box-folder 28 - 1)
    - Draft Statute: "United Nations Diplomatic Conference of the Plenipotentiaries on the Establishment of an International Criminal Court", 16 July 1998 (Box-folder 28 - 2)
      2 copies. 1 - Handwritten comments on a few pages, 2 - Different formatting and tabs
    - "Statute at a Glance" printout: "On the Record gives you a quick guide to the highlights in the ICC statute" (Box-folder 28 - 3)
      Handwritten notes and markup
    - Rome Treaty: Letter to Samuel Burger, National Security Advisor re: Clinton Administration's support for the UN's Rome Treaty establishing the ICC, 13 October 1999 (Box-folder 28 - 4)
      including notes and addendum (duplicate copy has been removed)
    - Rome Treaty: Letter to Henry A. Kissinger from Monroe Leigh Re: UN Rome Treaty est. ICC, 4 January 2001 (Box-folder 28 - 5)
      includes newspaper clippings and Leigh's responses
    - Rome Treaty: Newspaper photocopies regarding Clinton Administration and the UN's proposed ICC 2000 (Box-folder 28 - 6)
      1. "Slay This Monster" by Senator Jesse Helms, Financial Times, July 30, 1998, 2. "For Clinton's Last Act" by Robert S. McNamara &,amp, Benajmin B. Ferencz, NYTimes Op-Ed, Dec. 12, 2000, 3. "Internaitonal Court Pressures and Perils" by Ted Galen Carpenter, Washington Times Od-Ed, Dec. 26, 2000, 4. "Proposed International Court Will Protect Civil Liberties" by Monroe Leigh, Washington Times, Dec. 30, 2000 [duplicate copies of 3 &,amp,4 removed]
  - Sovereign Immunity
    - Sovereign Immunity Acts (photocopies), 1976, 1978 (Box-folder 28 - 7)
      1. State Immunity Act 1978 (United Kingdom), 2. Foreign Sovereign Immunities Act of 1976 (United States)
    - ILC Project: Memorandum re: Report of the Work Group on jurisdictional immunities of States and their property from Stephen Schwebel to Monroe Leigh, 14 August 1978 (Box-folder 28 - 8)
      Contains Stephen M. Schwebel signature
    - Articles: On Sovereign Immunity Acts, 1980, 1982 (Box-folder 28 - 9)
      1. Sovereign Immunity, Act of State, OPEC, April 1980, 2. Draft Articles for a Convention on Sovereign Immunity, February 9, 1982
    - Articles: "Foreign States Sued for Their Acts Abroad: A Uniform Analysis Under the Foreign Sovereign Immunities Act" by Gregory Haworth, Rutgers Law Review, Vol. 34, No. 3, Spring 1982, pp. 538 - 566. 1982 (Box-folder 28 - 10)
    - Articles: "State Immunity: Law and Practice in the United States and Europe" Proceedings of Conference held on November 17, 1978 at the University of London. International Law Assocation. 1978 (Box-folder 28 - 11)
      Contains October 9, 1980 letter inserted into pages from James Crawford to Monroe Leigh regarding previous correspondence on immunity
    - Articles: "Suing Foreign Governments in American Courts: the United States Foreign Sovereign Immuniites Act in Practice" by Beverly May Carl, Southwestern Law Journal, Vol. 33, No. 4, November 1979, pp. 1010 - 1077. November 1979 (Box-folder 28 - 12)
      Contains Business Card of Beverly May Carl with handwritten message "With best regards"
    - Articles: "Sovereign Immunity and Act of State: Correlative or Conflicting Policies?" by Harold G. Maier, University of Cincinnati Law Review, Vol. 35, 1966, pp. 556 - 577. 1966 (Box-folder 28 - 13)
      From Najbee Samie, Contains handwritten memo to Najbee Samie with questions
    - Articles: "The Attachment of Iranian Assets in West Germany - An Outline of the German Pre-judgement Procedure and the Doctrine of Sovereign Immunity" by Dr. Reinhard Dallmayr, Academy Review (International and Comparative Law Center), No. 5, January 1981, pp. 10 - 14 January 1981 (Box-folder 28 -)
    - Articles: "The Foreign Sovereign Immunities Act of 1976: Some Suggested Amendments" by Myres S. McDougal and Robin-Eve Jasper, Speech given to the Southwestern Legal Foundation June 1981 (Box-folder 28 - 14)
      Contains correspondence between Monroe Leigh and Myres S. McDougal, as well as edits
    - Articles: "Are Only 'Friendly' Foreign Governments Entitled to Sovereign Immunity?" by Gaylen J. Byker, International Practitioner's Notebook, No. 13, January 1981, pp. 1 - 4 January 1981 (Box-folder 28 - 15)
      Contains highlights, Memo stationary from Najeeb Samie
    - Articles: "Immunity and Jurisdiction: Toward a Uniform Body of Law in Actions Against Foreign States" by George Kahale, III and Matias A. Vega, Columbia Journal of Transnational Law, 18:211, 1979, pp. 211 - ? 1979 (Box-folder 28 -)
    - Articles: "The State Immunity Act of 1978: An English Update" by Stephan Bird, International Lawyer, n.d.? (Box-folder 28 - 16)
      Contains underlining
    - Articles: "Swiss Law and Practice in Relation to Measures of Execution Against the Property of a Foreign State," by Jean-Flavien Lalive, n.d.? (Box-folder 28 - 17)
    - Articles: [Manuscript] "Execution of Judgments and Foreign Sovereign Immunity" by James Crawford, American Journal of International Law, 29 December 1980 (Box-folder 28 - 18)
      Contains memorandum to Monroe Leigh re: Comments on suitability for publication, edits
    - Publications: "Immunity of State Property from Execution in the Yugoslav Legal System" by T. Varady, Netherlands Yearbook of Internatioanl Law, Vol. X, 1979, pp. 85 - 95 1979 (Box-folder 29 - 1)
    - Publications: Swedish and International Arbitration. Yearbook of the Arbitration Institute of the Stockholm Chamber of Commerce. 1982 (Box-folder 29 - 2)
    - Publications: "Arbitration and Choice-of-Law Clauses as Waivers of Jurisdictional Immunity" by George Kahale, III. New York University Journal of International Law and Politics. Vol. 14, No. 1, Fall 1981. pp. 29 - 63. 1981 (Box-folder 29 - 3)
      Contains note.
    - Publications: "Government and Industry in the Federal Republic of Germany" by Georg Ress. The International Law Quarterly, January 1980, pp. 87 - 111. January 1980 (Box-folder 29 - 4)
      Note: "With the compliments of the author"
    - Publications: "H.R. 11315 - The Revised State-Justice Bill on Foreign Sovereign Immunity: Time for Action" by Timothy Atkeson, Samuel Perkins, and Michael Wyatt. Reprinted from the American Journal fo International Law, Vol. 70, No. 2, April 1976, pp. 297 - 322. April 1976 (Box-folder 29 -)
    - Publications: Decisions of the British Courts articles by James Crawford for the British Year Book of International Law, 1974 - 1982 (Box-folder 29 - 5)
      1. "Decisions of British Courts During 1974-1975 Involving Questions of Public and Private Interntainal Law A. Public International Law" by Dr. James Crawford, 2. "Decisions of British Courts During 1974-1975 invovling Questions of Public and Private International Law A. Public International Law" by James Crawford, 3. "Decisions of British Courts During 1978 Involving Questions of Public and Private International Law" by James Crawford, 4. "Decisions of British Courts During 1980 Involving Questiosn of Public International Law" by James Crawford
    - Publications: "The Contribution of Professor D. P. O'Connell to the Discipline of International Law" by James Crawford, The British Year Book of International Law, Fifty-First Year of Issue, 1982 (Box-folder 29 - 6)
      Contains note from James Crawford.
    - Publications: "Execution of Judgments and Foreign Sovereign Immunity" by James Crawford. Reprinted from the American Journal of International Law, Vol. 75, No. 4, October 1981. pp. 820 - 869 1981 (Box-folder 29 - 7)
    - Publications: "A Foreign Sovereign Immunities Act for Australia?" by James Crawford and Letter 16 September 1981 (Box-folder 29 - 8)
      Contains letter from James Crawford to Monroe Leigh.
    - Publications: Working Paper No. 1: "Pre-Judgment attachment of State property: the law in some Commonwealth jurisdictions." International Law Association (Australian Branch), Committee on Sovereign Immunity. August 1980 (Box-folder 29 - 9)
      Contains correspondence between Monroe Leigh and James Crawford.
    - Publications: "Recent Developments in the Dynamics of Sovereign Immunity" by Gamal Moursi Badr. The American Journal of Comparative Law. Vol 30, 1982. pp.678 - 683. 1982 (Box-folder 29 -)
    - Publications: "Jurisdiction Over Organs and Officials of States. The Holy See and Intergovernmental Organisations" by Finn Seyersted. Reprinted from The Internatioanl and Comparative Law Quarterly. January - April 1965. pp. 33 - 80 and 493 - 527. 1965 (Box-folder 29 -)
    - Publications: "Immunity from Attachment and Execution" by Michael Brandon. Reprinted from International Financial Law Review (Box-folder 29 - 10)
      Contains note &,amp, business card from Michael Brandon
    - Publications: "Fifth Report on Jurisdictional Immunities of States and their Property" by Mr. Sompong Sucharitkul. UN, International Law Commission, 35th Session, Geneva, May 3 - July 22, 1983, A/CN.4/363, 22 March 1983 (Box-folder 29 - 11)
      Contains memo note from William E. Hannaford to Monroe Leigh
    - Publications: "Report of the International Law commission on the work of its thirty-fifth session" 3 May - 22 July 1983, General Assembly, Official Records: Thirty-Eighth Session Supplement No. 10 (A/38/10) 1983 (Box-folder 29 -)
    - Publications: "Jurisdictional Immunities of States and their Property. Information and materials submitted by Governments. Addendum." UN, International Law Commission Thirty-third session, 4 May - 24 July, 1981, (A/CN.4/343/Add.3) 5 May 1981 (Box-folder 29 -)
    - Publications: "Jurisdictional Immunities of States and their Property. Information and materials submitted by Governments. Addendum." UN, International Law Commission Thirty-third session, 4 May - 24 July, 1981, (A/CN.4/343/Add.1) 16 April 1981 (Box-folder 29 -)
    - Publications: "Jurisdictional Immunities of States and their Property. Information and materials submitted by Governments." UN, International Law Commission, Thirty-third session, 4 May - 24 July 1981, (A/CN.4/343) 14 April 1981 (Box-folder 29 - 12)
    - Publications: "Fourth Report on Jurisdictional Immunities of States and their Property" by Sompong Sucharitkul, UN, International Law Commission, 34th Session, Geneva, 3 May - 23 July 1982 (A/CN.4/357), 31 March 1982 (Box-folder 29 - 13)
      Contains business card and note from Michael Brandon to Monroe Leigh
    - Publications: "Third Report on Jurisdictional Immunities of States and their Property" by Sompong Sucharitkul. UN, International Law Commission, Thirty-third session, Geneva, 4 May - 24 July 1981. (A/CN.4/340) 27 March 1981 (Box-folder 29 - 14)
      Contains note "With the Compliments of Michael Brandon"
    - Publications: "Second Report on Jursidtional Immunities of States and their Property" by Sompong Sucharitkul. Addendum. UN, International Law Commission, Thirty-second session, Geneva, 5 May - 25 July 1980. (A/CN.4/331/Add.1) 9 June 1980 (Box-folder 29 - 15)
      Contains correspondence between Stephen M. Schwebel and Monroe Leigh
    - Publications: "Second Report on Jursidtional Immunities of States and their Property" by Sompong Sucharitkul. UN, International Law Commission, Thirty-second session, Geneva, 5 May - 25 July 1980. (A/CN.4/331) 11 April 1980 (Box-folder 29 - 16)
    - Significant Cases: Materials related to Maritime International Nominees Establishment v. The Republic of Guinea, 1982 (Box-folder 29 - 17)
      Contains memorandum, correspondence, post-it notes,
    - Significant Cases: Materials related to Banks v. Sheikh Allal Al-Fassi, 1982 (Box-folder 29 - 18)
      Contains looseleaf paper, notes
    - Significant Cases: Materials related to International Association of Machinists vs. OPEC, 1979 (Box-folder 30 - 1)
      Contains handwritten memorandum, briefs, newspaper articles and transcripts of proceedings
    - Significant Cases: Materials related to uranium antitrust litigation, 1979 (Box-folder 30 - 2)
      Contains memrondum, brief, transcripts
    - Significant Cases: Materials related to Shell Petroleum, 1983 - 1984 (Box-folder 30 - 3)
      Contains transcipts and newspaper articles
    - Significant Cases: Materials related to Margaret Hitchcock &,amp, Wilber Hitchcock v. United States, 1979 (Box-folder 30 - 4)
      Contains transcripts and handwritten memos0000000000
    - Significant Cases: Materials related to various cases, 1979 - 1982 (Box-folder 30 - 5)
      Contains handwritten notes, underlines, articles
    - Eaglet Corp. v. Central Bank of Nicaragua: United States Court of Appeals for the 2nd Circuit, 94-7043, Apellate papers, 1994 (Box-folder 30 - 6)
      1. Brief of Plaintiff-Appellant, 2. Reply Brief of Plaintiff-Appellant, 3. Brief of Defendant-Appellee, 4. Joint Appendix
  - International Law Association Committee on State Immunity
    - Heidelburg Meeting: Correspondence, May and July 1989, November 1988 (Box-folder 30 - 7)
      Contains handwritten notes, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh &,amp, Georg Ress,
    - Heidelburg Meeting: Meeting Materials, October 1989 (Box-folder 30 - 8)
      Contains handwritten notes and yellow pad pages, Agenda and Participants
    - Heidelburg Meeting: Reports, September 1989 and June 1988 (Box-folder 30 - 9)
      1. Report on Developments in United States Sovereign Immunity Practice submitted by Monroe Leigh, September 28, 1989, 2. Interim Report Committee on State Immunity by Monroe Leigh, Draft June 17, 1988
    - Heidelburg Meeting: Summaries, Findings, Memoranda, July and October 1989 (Box-folder 30 - 10)
      1. AJIL International Decisions Section, 2. Summary of research on state immunity doctrine - case law, 3. Attachment and Execution of Property and Foreign Sovereign Immunity, 4. Foreign State Immunity: Summary of Law Review Articles Relevant to the American Experience with the Seven Questions Proposed in the Warsaw Report of the International Law Association Committee on State Immunity
    - Heidelburg Meeting: Reports, 1989 (Box-folder 30 - 11)
      Reports from: Georg Ress, Ajit Kumar Sengupta, Tara Kishore Prasad, Tibor Varady, Gamal Badr, Christopher H. Schreuer, C.C.A. Voskuil, Renata Sonnenfeld, Lady Fox, Giovanni de Sangro,
    - Heidelburg Meeting: ILA Warsaw Conference (1988) Interim Report of the Committee on State Immunity 1988 (Box-folder 30 - 12)
    - Heidelburg Meeting: October 13, 1989, Meeting Materials 13 October 1989 (Box-folder 30 - 13)
      Contains handwritte notes and phone numbers
    - Saarbrucken Meeting - April: Conference / Travel Information, 1991 (Box-folder 31 - 1)
      Contains pencil markup and comments
    - Saarbrucken Meeting - April: Program materials, 1989 (Box-folder 31 - 2)
    - Saarbrucken Meeting - April: Articles re: State Immunity, n.d. (Box-folder 31 - 3)
    - Saarbrucken Meeting - April: Papers for the Conference on State Immunity of the Internatioanl Law Assocaition in Saarbrucken (October 21-23, 1993) Professor Georg Ress (Rapporteur) 21 - 23 October 1993 (Box-folder 31 - 4)
    - Saarbrucken Meeting - October: Conference / Travel Information, 1993 (Box-folder 31 - 5)
      Contains notations
    - Saarbrucken Meeting - October: Articles re: Conference topic, 1961, 1990, 1993 (Box-folder 31 - 6)
    - Saarbrucken Meeting - October: Materials re: Conference, Sept - Oct. 1993 (Box-folder 31 - 7)
    - Saarbrucken Meeting - October: Handwritten notes, 1993 (Box-folder 31 - 8)
      Contains handwritten notes and diagram of setting arrangement
    - Saarbrucken Meeting - October: Correspondence re: Conference, Aug - Oct 1993 (Box-folder 31 - 9)
      Contains signature of Monroe Leigh
    - Vol. I: Correspondence, 1987 - 1988 (Box-folder 31 - 10)
      Contains post-it notes and handwritten comments, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, F. L. de May, Pierre Lalive, Ian Brownlie, B. Osorio, Ricardo R. Balestra, Silvia Maureen Williams, Georg Ress, Sueo Ikehara, Finn Syerstad, Tibor Varady, James Crawford, Rodney N. Purvis, Najeeb Samie, Edward Gordon, Gamal Badr, Kanae Taijudo, O. V. Bogdanov, Helmut SteinBurger, Ian Sinclair, Lars Hjerner, Michael M. Gondwe, K. M Ioannou
    - Vol. I: Meeting Materials - Warsaw, 1988 (Box-folder 31 - 11)
      Contains handwritten note pages, post-it notes, comments
    - Vol. I: Drafts &,amp, Draft Materials, 1987 - 1988 (Box-folder 31 - 12)
      Contains post-it notes and instructions for Summer associates
    - Vol. I: Reports &,amp, Articles, 1982, 1987 (Box-folder 31 - 13)
      1. Interim Report Committee on State Immunity, 6/15/88, 2. International Law Assoication Montreal Conference (1982) International Committee on State Immunity Report
    - Vol. II: Correspondence, 1989 - 1990 (Box-folder 31 - 14)
      Contains post-its and handwritten notes, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Georg Ress, Barbara Osorio, Najeeb Samie, F. L. de May, K. W. Cuperus, Ian Brownlie,
    - Vol. II: Resolutions / Draft Articles, 27 October 1989 and 3 August 1990 (Box-folder 31 - 15)
      1. 3 alternate resolutions for the Queensland Conference, 2. Review of Professor Ress's Preliminary Report on Developments in State Immunity (Montreal Draft Convention)
    - Vol. II: Reports, 1989 - 1990 (Box-folder 31 - 16)
      1. Report for the ILA Conference in Queensland, 2. Amendment to the Foreign Sovereign Immunities Act and the Berman Bill from the House of Representatives, 3. Injunctions under sovereign immunity law, 4. Summary of Law Review Articles relevant to the American Experience with the Seven Questions Proposed in teh Warsaw Report of the International Law Association Committee on State Immunity.
    - Vol. II: Meeting Materials - Queensland Conference, August 19 - 26, 1990 (Box-folder 31 - 17)
    - Vol. III: Correspondence, January - April, 1991 (Box-folder 32 - 1)
      Signature: Monroe Leigh, Correspondents include: Jiri Zemanek, Monroe Leigh, Georg Ress, Christine De Witt,
    - Vol. III: Meeting Materials, March - April 1991 (Box-folder 32 - 2)
      List of Participants and Agenda for April 4 - 6, 1991 Meeting
    - Vol. III: Drafts of Articles and Reports, March - April 1991 (Box-folder 32 - 3)
      Contains mark-up, post-its, handwritten notes
    - Vol. III: Articles and Court Decisions about State Immunity, 1990 - 1991 (Box-folder 32 - 4)
    - Vol. III: Handwritten Notes, Saarbrucken Meeting, 5 - 6 April 1991 (Box-folder 32 - 5)
      Contains diagrams of seating arrangment as well as notes about panels and discussions
    - Vol. IV: Meeting Materials, 1991 (Box-folder 32 - 6)
      Contains post-it, Participants for ILA Committee on State Immunity April 4-6, 1991, Cairo Conference 1992 Guidelines for Reports
    - Vol. IV: Correspondence, 1991 - 1992 (Box-folder 32 - 7)
      Contains handwritten notes, markup, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Raul Vinuesa, Georg Ress, P.J. O'Keefe, Jurgen Brohmer, Catherin Kessedjian, Christoph Schreuer, Jiri Zemanek, Tibor Varady,
    - Vol. IV: Reports / Draft Articles, 1991 - 1992 (Box-folder 32 - 8)
      Contains post-its, handwritten notes, edits, markup, 1. UN: International Law Commission Report on the Draft Aricles Adopted at its 43rd Session, 2. Committee on Cultural Heritage Law, ILA, Report and Draft Convention for Consideration at the 1992 Conference, 3. Montreal Draft Article I/ILC Draft Article 2 (versions and edits), 4. ILA, State Immunity - Dissenting opinion, 5. Jurisdictional Immunities of States and their Property (UN, A/CN.4/L.457)
    - Vol. V: Meeting Materials, 1992 - 1994 (Box-folder 32 - 9)
      Contains post-its, handwritten markup and notes
    - Vol. V: Articles &,amp, Papers on Immunity, 1992 - 1993 (Box-folder 32 - 10)
    - Vol. V: Correspondence, 1992 - 1993 (Box-folder 32 - 11)
      Contains post-its, markup, notes, and handwritten comments
    - Vol. VI: Correspondence, Jan 1994 - June 1995 (Box-folder 32 - 12)
    - Vol. VI: Materials re: Committee, 1994, June 1998 (Box-folder 32 - 13)
    - Vol. VI: Drafts re: proposed publication on immunity, May and June 1995 (Box-folder 32 - 14)
      Contains signature of Monroe Leigh, handwritten notes, edits
    - Shadow Committee - American Branch: Correspondence & Journal articles, 1985, 1990 - 1991 (Box-folder 32 - 15)